

CONTACT DETAILS

Mobile Number: (+63) 917 503 0797 Email Address: papilla.jennyr@gmail.com

CORE QUALIFICATIONS

- Management of an I.T. Support team
- Basic hardware and Software troubleshooting
- Understanding of direct marketing concepts
- Familiarity with Rich Media and the interactive space
- Immense experience in store management activities
- Theoretical knowledge of business management and exposure to real-time store trading activities
- Knowledge in Visual Basic, JavaScript, HTML, HTML 5, Flash CS5.5, ERP System and PeopleSoft, MS Visio,
- Developing/ Designing Processes and Procedures
- Drawing Process Flows and Flowcharts
- System Analysis and Process Analysis
- Proficient in Microsoft Office
- Strong negotiating skills and experience in dealing with a wide variety of people at different levels
- Flexible, self-motivated and resourceful
- Has an eye for detail, organized and structured in approaching problems
- Accounting literate

JENNY PAPILLA

OBJECTIVE

Led the IT team through several big projects from start to finish, and have worked as a consultant. I am confident my management skills, business acumen and knowledge in analyzation of processes are ideal for the position available in your company.

EDUCATION

DeLaSalleUniversity-Dasmariñas 2004Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

WORK EXPERIENCE

TASKUS | CAVITE, PHILIPPINES

IT Supervisor | March 2022 - May 2023

- Handled multiple locations Globally for TaskUs
- Lead IT Support Specialist across TU sites
- Checking daily tickets and monitoring ticket SLA
- Prepares weekly report for unreturned assets and asset deployments
- Leads asset cycle counting across sites
- Doing random asset sampling during audits
- · Leading monthly and quarterly audits
- Conducting physical full inventory
- Coordinates with different departments, attends meetings involving IT assets
- Responsible for the performance management of I.T. team
- Responsible for ITSS scheduling
- Conducting weekly one-on-one coaching and team meeting

Operations Team Leader | May 2019 - March 2022

- Work closely with the team, motivating and coaching them
- Conduct One-on-One coaching and team meetings
- Making sure the team reach their targets
- Support the Operations Manager to highlight operational risks and areas for improvement
- Work with the management team to identify and deliver positive change and business efficiencies
- Escalate any appropriate problems to proper department
- Support the Senior Manager to highlight operational risks and areas for improvement
- · Manage team KPI

CONTACT DETAILS

Mobile Number: (+63)917 503 0797 Email Address: papilla.jennyr@gmail.com

JENNY PAPILLA

ABUISSA HOLDING | DOHA, QATAR

IT COORDINATOR / IT PROCESS CONSULTANT | December 2013 — April 2019

- Designing and drawing flowcharts
- Analyzing flows for new system development
- Coordination and support for I.T. teams from UAE, KSA, New York, Turkey, Bahrain and Qatar
- · Started the asset management
- Handling IT assets
- Provides asset reports and ITSS performance reports
- Managing IT Assets from acquisition, setup to disposal and inventory.
- · Conducting IT asset quarterly audits
- Doing quarterly and yearly inventory
- Handling of POS installations and troubleshooting when the need arises
- Responsible for managing the IT aspect in project implementation such as preparation and installation of peripheral devices, network set-up and POS configuration for new outlets
- Responsible for deleting, creating email addresses and profiles in AD
- Conducting new systems training
- Develops new processes and policies
- Develop forms for the IT Department
- System implementation
- Implements beta testing (UAT)
- Conducting training for newly develop systems

COGNIZANT TECHNOLOGY SOLUTIONS | TAGUIG, PHILS.

SR. PROCESS EXECUTIVE / CAMPAIGN MANAGER | June 2012 — November 2013

- Develop and maintain relationships with clients, technology partners, agencies and creative shops
- Manage multiple concurrent campaigns, including launching, monitoring, analyzing and communicating effective and ineffective areas of a campaign
- Work effectively with a variety of internal teams, including Sales, Engineering, Product Management, and other Client Services teams
- Expand personal and team knowledge of new and upcoming products, such as mobile and dynamic ads
- Effectively maintain client expectations and meet deadlines

JENNY PAPILLA

CONTACT DETAILS

Mobile Number: (+63)917 503 0797 Email Address: papilla.jennyr@gmail.com

NATY JOEL TRADING - WESTERN UNION | CAVITE, PHILS.

OUTLET MANAGER | November 2009 - May 2012 (Part Time 2009-2011; full time 2011-2012

- Responsible for meeting the profit goals of the establishment
- In charge of managing operations on a daily basis
- Oversees employee training and ensure that all hourly employees complete their training in a timely manner
- Handles and resolves customer complaints
- Ensures that the cash registers have an adequate supply of change and bills
- Acts as liaison between Western Union and Store Franchisee

TELETECH | BACOOR, CAVITE

Aug 2007 - Oct 2011

LEADAGENT (SUPERVISOR)

- Provided leadership to a team of technical support representatives to ensure quality customer service and maintain Service Level Agreements
- Supervise daily operations in a technical support contact center environment
- Implemented in depth coaching/training to new and tenured technical support representatives
- Achieved business objectives and performance goals by working together with top management in ensuring operational efficiencies through planning, continuous monitoring, and analysis of the technical support call center operation
- Managed multiple priorities as well as motivate and lead the support team
- Provided level 1 and 2 support for a North American ISP

TECHNICAL SUPPORT REPRESENTATIVE FOR INTERNET CONNECTION

- Perform advanced troubleshooting on internet connectivity over the phone or through remote computer access
- Escalate class issues and repair cases to appropriate party
- Analysis, diagnosis and resolution of client problems

JENNY PAPILLA

CONTACT DETAILS

Mobile Number: (+63)917 503 0797 Email Address: papilla.jennyr@gmail.com

TEAMLEADER/TECHNICAL SUPPORT FOR LAPTOPS

- Analysis and troubleshooting of hardware and software problems of laptop computers, notebooks and peripheral devices
- Support for internet connectivity issues
- Escalate class issues and repair cases to appropriate party
- Perform advanced software repair installations
- Provide and coordinate quotation for out-of-warranty cases
- Implement system upgrade, perform system backups and disaster recovery
- As team leader: manage my team's KPI (key performance indicator) and do coaching sessions. Making sure the team meets the service level agreement of the client.

CERTIFICATIONS/TRAININGS

Culinary Arts and Culture Cookery - NC II March 2022 Cavite School of St. Mark

Rich Media Advertising Training January 2013 Cognizant Technology Solutions

E - Commerce Marketing Training June 2013 Cognizant Technology Solutions

ITILv3Certification March 2013 Cognizant Technology Solutions

ManagementTraining October 2008 Teletech Philippines March 2009 Western Union

S y s t e m A n a l y s i s a n d D e s i g n S y m p o s i u m August 2002 De La Salle University

A d v a n c e d V i s u a l B a s i c August 2002 De La Salle University

English Proficiency March 2004 De La Salle University